linkive.com 2012-08-04

# Linkive - Get Latest Links.

**Link** **ive** respects the privacy of the visitors to the Website, the home page of which is located at http://www. **Link** **ive** .com. This privacy policy is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information and Anonymous Information you submit to us through our Services and/or the **Link** **ive** toolbar (the "Toolbar"). Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms set forth in the Terms of Service for the **Link** **ive** Services 

### Personal Information You Provide to Us

**Link** **ive** does not collect any Personal Information about you (such as your name, email address, preferences.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The Personal Information we gather from you helps us learn about our members and potential members of our community and the users of the Toolbar. We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Service and/or the Toolbar. The types of Personal Information we collect are: 

  * When you sign up for our **Link** **ive** Services, we will collect your email address, name, date of birth and your gender.
  * When you personalize your **Link** **ive** Profile, we will collect any information you provide, such as your name or gender, address, phone number and any other optional information about you, your lifestyle, and your interests.
  * When you enter any information, including Personal Information, into any postings or comments within the **Link** **ive** Services, we will collect such information and this information might be available for some, a group/subgroup of, or even all members of the **Link** **ive** Services, depending on how and where this information was posted by you.
  * When you are signed into the **Link** **ive** toolbar and then when you sign-in to your account in gmail, AOL, yahoo, Linked-in etc through the browser, we will collect your contact names/mail-ids from your contact list upon your approval.
  * When you accept we will import your bookmarks/favorite links from your internet browser to your **Link** **ive** account.
  * When you enter your e-mail id and password of other mail/networking sites we will retrieve your contact list from those sites and store it in the contact list of your **Link** **ive** account.
  * When you leave us feedback, we will collect any information that is contained in your feedback.
  * When you contact us by sending us an e-mail, we will collect your e-mail address and any information contained in the e-mail you send us.

The **Link** **ive** Profile that you create when you sign up for our **Link** **ive** Services contains Personal Information such as your name, username, age, and location. Your personal details such as e-mail, date of birth, address and phone number are displayed only to friends present in your friend’s list. All other details are including your profile picture are readily visible to all **Link** **ive** members. This eases searching for friends in the **Link** **ive** user-group. Your username and general physical location may always be publicly displayed. 

### Use of Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used by us to sign you up for our community, respond to requests that you make, to improve our community and Services and to better tailor the features, performance and support of the Services and the Toolbar, and to offer you additional information, opportunities, and functionality. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails, should you request to receive such communications from us. Information you provide, with the exception of your email address, will also be displayed on your profile page which is viewable by other users of **Link** **ive** .  Please be aware that if you enter any Personal Information into publicly available sections of the **Link** **ive** Services, this information will be displayed to anyone who has access to these sections. These publicly available sections of the **Link** **ive** Services include, without limitation, posts and comments of other **Link** **ive** Members.  Your contact list information is mainly used to send invitations/alerts in the form of mails to users who are already not members of **Link** **ive** . And for contacts who are already members of **Link** **ive** , an alert is box is also displayed regarding the invitation/alert. In either of the cases your personal information is likely to be displayed to the other person in reference. We may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that make the information personally identifiable to you.  We may use this Anonymous Information to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance our community and Services.  We reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to third parties in our discretion. If we delete your account at your request, we will delete all Personal Information from the account, but we retain the right to maintain non-personally identifiable information about the account (e.g. date created, date terminated, shared links, etc.).  Also, if we terminate your account as allowed under the Terms of Service, we may choose to maintain all data collected from your use of the **Link** **ive** Services, including Personal Information. 

### Cookies and Log Files

Like most web sites, **Link** **ive** uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer and allows **Link** **ive** to recognize you as a member when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Cookies also help us understand how members use **Link** **ive** , which allows us to continually improve the service. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site. 

### Security

**Link** **ive** has implemented security measures to protect member information from loss, misuse and alteration. We use industry-standard practices such as encrypted storage, firewalls and password protection systems to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information. Each of our employees is aware of our security policies, and your information is only available to those employees who need it to perform their jobs. 

### Sharing Links

The primary feature of **Link** **ive** is to be able to share and view links that you share and those your friends share with you. The links that you share with your friends also get listed in your favorite links page. Any link, in the website, trailing with the share icon can further be shared with your friends. Using **Link** **ive** .com’s services or through the **Link** **ive** browser toolbar you can share links with your friends as well as other contacts present in your contact list. If you share a link with friends in your **Link** **ive** network, the link will be displayed in his/her links inbox and under a particular label. If you share a link with contacts other than those present in your **Link** **ive** network an e-mail, containing the link as well as invitation to join **Link** **ive** , is sent to them along with your personal information like your name and e-mail id. 

### Favorite Links

Your favorite links are best archived in **Link** **ive** and can be viewed in your **Link** **ive** account. Your favorite-links/bookmarks from your web-browser, when imported, will get listed in the favorite links section of the site. 

### Friends/Groups/Contacts

A useful feature of **Link** **ive** is the option to create groups within your friends. The groups and group names, as of now, solely belong to your account. When you create a group, we may ask you to provide information to identify the group, such as a group name, a unique abbreviation and a brief description of the group. Your contacts, when imported from other web-sites, are listed according to those web-site user-names. When you want to share a link you can share it with friends within **Link** **ive** as well as your other contacts who are non-members of **Link** **ive** . 

### GoLive

When you are on a particular web-site, this feature of **Link** **ive** toolbar allows you look-at and post comments on that web-site. The comments or information you provide through this feature is public to all **Link** **ive** users and **Link** **ive** is not responsible for any disclosure of your personal/private information while using this feature. 

### Other **Link** **ive** Members

You may invite a non-member of **Link** **ive** to register with the site and join your network or group. You also may invite existing **Link** **ive** members to become your direct contact. In these cases, **Link** **ive** generates an e-mail message to your invitee that may list information such as your e-mail address, your full name and your profile picture (if you have provided one). The rest of your contact information will only be shared with the person you invite if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish each other as contacts. In addition, when you visit another **Link** **ive** member's home page, we may share with that member your User ID and profile picture, if you've provided one. 

### Ratings and Feedback

When you click on the rating buttons in the Toolbar, you are explicitly sending information about your preferences for the site currently displayed in your browser. **Link** **ive** uses this information in order to gain insight into user-preferences and patterns of information access. If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Personal Information.  We will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Personal Information in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

### Invitations

As a **Link** **ive** Member you may invite others to join **Link** **ive** . **Link** **ive** shall process personal data collected in the course of the invitation solely for the invitation and shall not use it for any other purposes. Please note that the following sections of your Personal Data may be displayed to the recipient of the invitation: * Your photograph * Your name * Your E-mail ID 

### Search Functions

**Link** **ive** offers search functionality to find particular **Link** **ive** Members. The search functions can help you to initiate contact with other **Link** **ive** members who are probably your real life friends. Thus, you can find the contacts you need - and systematically expand your personal network. 

### Links to Other Web Sites

You see links to other web sites on **Link** **ive** , These links are posted by other **Link** **ive** members or have been shared by you, with your friends. **Link** **ive** is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites you may visit through a link you found on **Link** **ive** . If you provide information directly to a party other than **Link** **ive** , different privacy policies may cover those parties' use of your information. Please review any company's privacy policy before disclosing your personal information. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

**Link** **ive** may update this privacy policy. The latest version of the privacy policy will always be available at www. **Link** **ive** .com. Please check the privacy policy occasionally to make sure you are aware of any updates. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [admin@linkive.com](mailto:admin@linkive.com)
